{
    "subject": "resource/Moloya_Goswami",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Assam",
    "human_readable": "Moloya Goswami was born in Assam.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9056599140167236,
            "question": "Where was Moloya Goswami born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6268332004547119,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Assam besides Moloya Goswami?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2905804216861725,
            "question": "Is there a specific language spoken primarily in Assam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24875639379024506,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the culture of Assam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22671595215797424,
            "question": "What state is Assam known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21309742331504822,
            "question": "What is the history of Assam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14479759335517883,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Assam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14283521473407745,
            "question": "What are some notable landmarks or tourist attractions in Assam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14218157529830933,
            "question": "What are some popular festivals celebrated in Assam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12221487611532211,
            "question": "What is the geography of Assam like?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Moloya Goswami was born in Assam.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8573_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular festivals celebrated in Assam?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8573_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable landmarks or tourist attractions in Assam?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8573_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Assam?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8573_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8573_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8573_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8573_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8573_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8573_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8573_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8573_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8573_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8573_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8573_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Moloya Goswami was indeed born in Assam. According to the documents, she was born in Dibrugarh, which is a place in Assam."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Moloya Goswami's birthplace, stating that she was born in Dibrugarh, which is a town located in the state of Assam. Therefore, the statement \"Moloya Goswami was born in Assam\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}